KIKELET is a script font inspired by spring (kikelet means spring in Hungarian) I was experimenting with unusual style of forming the letters "y" "p" "s" "z" etc. Well, you'll see!  There are two ligaturtes to replace double"tt" and "tl" for readability. 

Free for personal use only. For commercial use please donate or contact me via myhandwritings@gmail.com 

If you have character / language extension requests, any questions or feedback for further improvement on this one feel free to contact me!

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772

